oh we found something so cool so I think
it's go 1.19 that started adding uh this
the ability to link to stuff uh
explicitly in the documentation go read
about it but check it so so this is this
is a common it out piece of code right
and I do cap cap K and I can there's no
documentation right but if I wrap it in
a bracket and I do this I get the
documentation pretty cool right so why
does that matter because sometimes when
you're when you're documenting an
interface like I did up here
you know I used to think oh hey why
should it put in it fills the driver
interface well I what's the driver
interface right and now I can do capital
K and I get that nice pretty interface
it's a really good thing look about read
about it you want to read about God dos
in 1.19 I'm in the middle of updating
all M but my heck make sure you put that
there because you'll make your
developers much happier